<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
  <category>
    <pattern>*</pattern>
    <template>Hello there! My name is CoCo. I will be your
    virtual assistant today. My job is to help you find a career path that best 
    fits you in the world of technology! 
    Please say "continue" when you are ready to proceed.</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
    <pattern>continue</pattern>
    <template>Great! Lets start by figuring out your interests!
    Are you a gamer and interested in the world of gaming? Do you find securing 
    networks and servers to be interesting? How about building websites for 
    businesses? Do you find Analyzing data statistics to be more of your 
    interest? Or do you like coding in SQL and administrating a database?
    Please respond with one option of "gaming", "security", "websites", "analysis", or 
    "administrating".</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>administrating</pattern>
      <template>An interest in administration will lead you down the path of
      being a Database Administrator. You are responsible for the proper placement
      of data, being that it is stored, retrieved, and secured correctly! This 
      career path plays a cruitial role in all businesses! If you would like to 
      hear the options again please say "continue" if not say "goodbye".</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>analysis</pattern>
      <template>If you are interested in analysis, becoming a Data Scientist
      might just be the path for you! A data scientist studies business data
      to optimize resources and adapt for constant growth. Looking at numbers all 
      day and developing algorithms is what its all about! If you would like to hear
      the options again please say "continue" if not say "goodbye".</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>websites</pattern>
      <template>Web Development is a fantastic career path. Every business
      needs one and you creativity can run wild! They are responsible for
      front end development and making the webpage as user friendly as possible.
      Some might say a functional website is the backbone of a business! If you
      would like to hear the options again please say "continue" if not say 
      "goodbye".</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>security</pattern>
      <template>Security is my personal favorite! You will be looking at the
      Information Security Analyst path. This path involves protecting an
      organizations computer networks and data from cyberattacks and data 
      breaches! If you would like to hear the options again please say 
      "continue" if not say "goodbye".</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>gaming</pattern>
      <template>Oh more of a gamer I see! Sounds like you would like
      game development. There are multiple paths you can take in the world
      of gaming. Specifically you could look into being a Gameplay Programmer,
      or a Graphics Programmer. If you would like more information on
      either of these topics please respond with either "Gameplay Programmer" or
      "Graphics Programmer".</template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>Graphics Programmer</pattern>
      <Template>A Graphics programmer specifically deals with visual aspects
      of the game such as rendering, shaders, and special effects. You goal would
      be to optimize performance for smooth gameplay! If you would like to hear
      the options again please say "continue" if not say "goodbye".</Template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
    <pattern>Gameplay Programmer</pattern>
    <template>A Gameplay programmer focuses on game mechanics, player controls
    and overall game behavior. You will need strong knowledge in C++ or C#! 
    If you would like to hear the options again please say "continue" if not 
    say "goodbye".
    </template>
  </category>
  
  <category>
      <pattern>goodbye</pattern>
      <template>
          Goobye and fairwell! I wish you the best of luck on your chosen career
          path! I hope I helped you find the right one!
      </template>
  </category>
</aiml>
